

Ravi Patel

Senior Front-end Developer

- +91 7016063230
- patelravi1611@gmail.com
- https://patelravi1611.github.io/
- m www.linkedin.com/in/patelravi1611/
- Bē www.behance.net/patelravi1611

Hi! I'm Ravi - a Front End Developer based in Ahmedabad. My work is deeply rooted in clean coding approach, with think outside the box mindset.

Combining research, strategy and visual best practices to create distinct impactful experiences.

I completed my Bachelor Degree in Computer engineering at the Universal Collage of Engineering & Technology in Ahmedabad.

- Born on November 16,1992
- Lives in Ahmedabad, India

Work Experience

Jetbro Pvt. Ltd.

React Js Developer (2019 - Present)

Jetbro Pvt. Ltd.

Senior Front-end Developer (2017 - 2019)

Step2Websoft Technology

Front-end Developer (2016 - 2017)

Shreedhoon Technology

Web Designer (2014 - 2015)

Education

Universal Collage of Engineering & Technology

Class of 2010; B.E Computer engineer

Skills

- HTML, CSS, Scss/Sass
- React Native
- Cross-Browser Development
- Git/Version Control
- Shopify

- JAVASCRIPT
- React Js/Next Js
- AWS/GCP

Docker

Projects

- Pluckk
- PIUCKK
- Beardo
- Marico
- Vibe
- Haiskn
- Pluckk App

- Ludic
- Parachute
- Addendo
- Aava
- Tubduk